[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elmali Kilise, a rock sanctuary built in Byzantine style, dates back to the Comnenan period and is located in which district?", "correct_answer": "Cappadocia", "incorrect_answers": ["Athens", "Sicily", "Istanbul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Duckie fight with in the hallway after he overhears him talking badly about Andie in the movie Pretty in Pink?", "correct_answer": "Steff", "incorrect_answers": ["Blane", "Pete", "Tom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Freezing does not change the structure of milk.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important nutrient is the pineapple fruit rich in?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Manganese", "Vitamin C", "Vitamin B1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the names of the two brothers who educate Sam about Santa Carlas vampire population in the movie The Lost Boys?", "correct_answer": "Edgar and Alan Frog", "incorrect_answers": ["Edgar and Alan Poe", "Sam and Michael Emerson", "Edgar and Alan Toad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which sport did actor Richard Gere excel when he was in high school?", "correct_answer": "Gymnastics", "incorrect_answers": ["Baseball", "Boxing", "Football"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was invented by Levi Spear Parmly?", "correct_answer": "Dental floss", "incorrect_answers": ["The jet engine", "Blue Ray discs", "The QWERTYU keyboard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Little Rock is the capital and most populous city of this US state.", "correct_answer": "Arkansas", "incorrect_answers": ["Wichita", "Kansas", "Topeka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to fly solo nonstop around the world in a balloon?", "correct_answer": "Steve Fossett", "incorrect_answers": ["Heinrich Kubis", "Richard Rutan", "John Alcock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The formation of toes in salamanders, animals that typically have no such organs, is an example for what?", "correct_answer": "Atavism", "incorrect_answers": ["Biometry", "Disturbance", "Biota"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Rothschilds were one of the most successful business families in history. Their family name literally means this.", "correct_answer": "Red Shield", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Shire", "Red Sheath", "Red Sheave"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happened to Nick Marshall (Mel Gibson), that caused him to hear womens thoughts in the 2000 comedy What Women Want?", "correct_answer": "He was electrified", "incorrect_answers": ["He slipped in the bathroom and hit his head", "He fell from his balcony", "He was hit by a truck"]}]